If every one user is more valuable for
me because I have high margins, I can
spend much more money on one user than
my competitors because I am making more
money out of out of that user. So like
it gives them a certain edge which they
could eventually use as well.
>> What's up everybody? It's LGD here and
welcome to Milk Road Stocks, the daily
market show that has a new mission in
life. Become the number one influencer
for companies that no one has ever heard
about. Today is September 29th, 2026.
What the hell is bending spoons? Until a
few weeks ago, no one at Milk Gro or
probably even in our audience, although
you guys are pretty sharp, knew about
this company. But ever since Vincent
gave us a deep dive on the business just
a few weeks back, it has caught the eye
of other investors here on our team.
Today, Martin, our lead researcher, is
on the show to present his own in-depth
valuation model for this very unique
business that basically acquires slow
growth software companies and
revitalizes them using AI and turns them
into very profitable businesses. We get
pretty technical on this show, but at
the end, Martin will reveal whether he's
got this one in his portfolio or not.
So, make sure you stick with us. And if
you do want to see what he is investing
in right now, it's just a dollar to take
a peek at his portfolio at the link
below and to catch the next wave of the
AI trade whenever it gets going. Martin,
good morning. Today, we're going to talk
about Bending Spoons. And this is a
company that I didn't know existed until
a few weeks ago when Vincent told us
about it. I only just realized the last
couple days that I guess it's a a like
Matrix analogy, right? Because you're
bending the spoon. The little kid is
bending the spoon. Although, I don't
know, maybe that's not what the name is
supposed to be. But I I I assume that
that's the main reason that it's called
bending spoons, but we're going to learn
a lot more about it today than just what
it's what the name is based on.
>> You're actually right that that's the
idea behind it.
>> It is. Okay. Okay. Okay. So, it's like
using your mind to bend something or
just like that they're going to do
something cool. They're going to do
something that you didn't think was
possible. Yeah. That kind of thing.
Cool. Okay, great. So, today I'm going
to talk about bending spoons. Obviously,
we have been looking at bending spoons
over the past few weeks as LG said and
you know we had a good discussion with
Winend about bending spoons because we
both really like the company. We both
built a different model and today I want
to present you with my model which
suggest in my base case that the fair
value for this company should be
something around 40 48 bucks which is um
45% higher than the current price. And
so I'm going to walk you through my
model and I'm going to share my rational
and my assumption so you can make your
own opinion and make your own judgment.
>> When you say model, what do you mean?
Like what's what's the difference
between you and Vincent's model? What is
what are your models? How do you come
how do you come up with your models?
>> I think we use the same kind of approach
because you have multiple ways how you
can build a model. So maybe it's you are
trying to predict their future cash
flows or maybe you are just trying to
summarize the different parts of their
business at the current value. Like
there are different ways how you can
approach this and I think we have
similar approach but we have different
assumptions. So like I'm going to
present my assumptions and why I think
these numbers are kind of my own
estimates and why I believe that these
numbers are you know relevant and they
are fair to to have.
>> Got it. Okay, that makes sense. Let's
get into it. Obviously, right now,
Bending Spoons trading 33 bucks and my
base case or my my fair value right now
should be much higher and something
around 48 bucks. But
before before I explain everything, I
should share some context about what
spending what bending spoon does and how
they make money. And [clears throat]
so today, Bending Spoons is a company
that's buying different companies. And
right now the market cap is 42 billion.
Um they have debt 5 billion. So if you
look at the companies, you should not
only look at market cap because you are
also buying the debt. So like enterprise
value is right now 247 billion. they're
making um like 2026
uh guidance for the revenue are at 2.8
billion and their adjusted operating
margins are 45%
which is pretty good and
we also have to say they have made over
50 acquisitions since they started. So
it's not a newcomer because right now it
feels like this market is getting very
hot and like you know because the idea
is super compelling like everyone wants
to use AI but only few like companies
know how to use AI effectively. So like
bending bending spoons is not saying
like hey we have got a solution for you.
They are saying we know how to use AI
but we are gonna acquire you and we are
going to just transform your business.
And you can see some some of their
numbers here. So they are growing um
pretty nicely over the last few years.
And yeah this should kind of set up the
context for the whole company. And just
so you know of their current portfolio,
all the companies that they own today,
they have access to five million monthly
active users across all these platforms.
And you know that's pretty insane
number. There's 7 8 billion people on
this planet and they have access to 500
million monthly active users. So um not
all of them are paying obviously but you
know if you bring that operational
excellence to those companies at some
point you will be able to monetize them
somehow. Um and so that's a pretty
pretty huge asset to have.
>> It also feels like it's it's it's
different. So, I just have a comment on
this as I've been learning more about it
from Vincent and now from you've been
hearing you talk too. It's that a lot of
the companies that you guys cover on on
our episodes, it's like they have they
have some kind of end client that they
serve in some way, right? It's like
they're going to be another enterprise
or hyperscaler or something like that.
This company is unique in the way that
it's like yes they do have clients but
they have 500 million they don't really
have clients they have 500 million
active users across a variety of
products and the whole model is to
continue to evolve what they're offering
those people. So it's like they don't
really it's not really like oh well if
the demand for their compute slows down
then they're not going to be able to you
know what I mean it's it's it's way
different than like an infraplay. This
is like, no, no, no. They're just buying
up companies that haven't evolved and
and their customers and then
transforming it and and their their
sauce is that they know how to use AI
really well. That's the that's that's
that's what's so unique about them. And
I think that I think it's such a a cool
idea and it's and I didn't realize there
was a company that's already so advanced
at doing this, right? I think it's so
cool.
>> Yeah. And uh also the founders they
they've had a startup before it failed
and the reason is that they said they
couldn't find like the distribution the
users and so right now they are not
necessarily like looking for companies
that will need to find the distribution.
They are already buying existing
companies with huge user bases. And so
like you know they are just saying like
hey you have huge user base that's all
we need because everything else that's
what we can do but the the the most
critical and most difficult part is to
get users that's like and even with AI
it's it's even getting like more visible
because right now everyone can build
like you know we were just talking about
how powerful these AI models are and so
like build software is pretty easy but
like they have the users already so they
don't need to do anything else to get
them because again it's getting very
very tricky and complicated but at the
same time just don't get me wrong like I
don't think people will go and they will
try to build their own notion or
streamyard we are just you know using
streamyard like like yes it's easy but
not not that easy so you can build
something like this at scale Right,
>> we're going to pause for a second. The
AI trade is changing. The bottleneck
stocks are either running out of steam
or getting ready for another leg higher
while the application layer is finally
starting to show some real profits. Our
analysts were early to the last wave and
now they are buying for the next one.
Catch your next call inside Milkro Pro
for just a dollar at the link below.
>> I get it. Yeah. So it's it's not it's
it's also you know and you you and Kyle
talk so much about software companies
and kind of where they're at in the
evolution of that and you're right that
it's like yes there's a lot of companies
that can be vibe coded with anthropic or
with cloud but it's like things like
what we're using right now. It's like
you're pretty far away from being able
to vibe code a a streaming platform that
probably I mean Streamyard must have a
lot of users is the most common common
platform there is in the industry and
it's and it processes a lot of data on a
daily basis right and it works
incredibly well. It's gonna be really
hard to vibe code that at that scale,
right? So, there's still a lot of value
in these these software companies and
then Streamyard is not one of their
companies, but like you're saying is
that it's it's there's a middle ground
there of stuff that can't just be
reinvented by vibe coding overnight.
>> Exactly. Yeah. And this is again just
like what they do like put it very
simply. Um they buy cheaply, fix
quickly, run for cash and repeat. That's
that's their whole kind of strategy.
That's the whole thing.
>> It sounds very easy. Um, and it actually
is easy. Like if you have all the tools
and like everything in place, it is
actually easy and it's repeatable
process. And the more you do it, the
better you get it at it. And like you
know that's how you create your kind of
unique insights and that's how you I'll
talk about like economics of scale a
little bit later. So right now they just
buy companies at like very low revenue
multiples usually usually around 2.5 um
the two latest acquisitions were Air
Table it cost them 2.7 uh multiple
revenue multiples and Mirror at 2.3
revenue multiples and it also takes them
some time to kind of transform all these
companies bring them onto their platform
and like make sure that the margins are
there at at the goal that they want. And
so like in my model I think like for the
first year they are certainly not going
to hit like 50 50% margins. So in my
model I assume well they actually said
that for um AOL they were able to
transform the company in like 9 months
at least 90% of that. So like you know
sometimes it's quicker sometimes it's
slower. I I I tend to be more
conservative and so I said I'm saying
like maybe the first year they might be
able just to get like 30% margins for
these companies. In the second year it's
might not be full full year like full
margin but their target is something
around 50% margins because that's how
that's that's what they are bringing.
They're bringing that operating
leverage, meaning you don't need as many
employees and as many things and tools.
You can just like use our whole platform
that will do a lot of work for you and
it will just increase your margins to
the way we want them and it's about 40%.
And the the company right now their
adjusted margins are at 40 44% at 54%
sorry. So like again my assumption is
they they are going to be somewhere
around 50%. I think that's what usually
the the team is kind of guiding towards
it's 50%. And then you know it starts it
those companies it starts to make money
like the higher margins the more profit
and then you you take that those profits
and you fund another acquisition. And so
that's kind of the flywheel that they're
doing and I'll talk later how this kind
of learnings compound and that's how you
build actually something pretty pretty
amazing I think. So here um I want to
tell you how we are looking at bending
spoons. Me and Winson we both kind of
look at this through the same lens
because there is already some existing
portfolio of companies and then there is
the second part which is like okay if
this kind of deal machine is really
working what's what's the future kind of
value of of that machine. So the current
the current portfolio is worth something
around 13 bucks or 15 30 I have here 13
bucks per share. Okay. So that's that's
how you get if you look at the existing
portfolio how much money those companies
are making today how much profits they
are making how much cash they are making
and then you can use some multiples and
try to forecast all their revenues
coming in over the next 10 years. Then
you just discount all that money back to
today's value and you get the value of
$13 per share. That's the part that's
already existing portfolio. So like
assuming they are not going to do any
more trades, any more deals, this is
what they have right now. So it kind of
represents the floor for the company. I
don't think that the stock share the
price should follow like should fall
below those levels like because it just
doesn't make much sense and if so it
means that the whole future the whole
platform value is zero which I don't
think it's the case. So the second part
is the platform
which is they have built their whole
operating system and now they are as
they are making more money they want to
deploy more money and put more money
into new acquisitions and kind of grow
their portfolio of businesses and that's
very valuable. I think I put it here.
It's I'll I'll walk you through exactly
how I got this number, but I think it's
worth about 30 bucks per share. And then
we have scale scale economies, which
means the more companies you have on
this operating system kind of the better
the cost can split between more
companies. Plus you are learning because
you you'll get more data and so you you
you kind of test your uh your flywheel
or like your knowhow like more
frequently which lets you iterate and
improve your whole process all the time.
So like you improve and it makes your
margins even better, your success rate
even higher and it kind of makes your
company much more valuable and much more
competitive. It actually gives you that
advantage that like any anyone else who
is maybe you know trying to be like solo
would struggle to compete with because
they they will just not be able to build
all these software and all these things
inhouse. So that's the the platform
value and then there is financing
because they are using debt and I see a
lot of people think that using debt is
is dangerous and scary and it is uh I
will be honest there but here they want
to use it because they can deduct all
these interest rates from their profits
and their cash. So it's actually good if
you finance the future growth with your
debt because it's deductible and it kind
of gives you gives you advantage. That's
why people and like look at hyperscalers
they have hundreds of billions of money
and yet they issue that and the reason
is because it just makes sense like you
should use depth if you if you if you
have the option like if there is an
upside if there's an opportunity you
should take it and use use that. So like
if you combine all these three things,
we get into 48 bucks and now the rest of
the presentation will be like I'll walk
you through each of these and explain
what's behind it.
>> You know, this this might seem kind of
basic, but I've never seen a model where
somebody just takes all the different
parts of the business and adds them
numerically to create a value per share.
I I don't know maybe you guys have never
done that for me but it's just I find
that interesting to do that to take like
to construct the value per share based
on different components which I think is
pretty cool. I mean that's
>> well it's getting actually pretty
frequent like even
>> usually do it for companies that have
different businesses like um
>> I think I did it with Galaxy because
Galaxy is you know crypto company and
the AI company. So you cannot just kind
of put it all together and use kind of
one approach. So you need to kind of
value each business separately and then
just add them up and it will give you
the the final the final uh result. Okay.
So
this is their current portfolio. It's uh
right now they have about um 4 billion
um in revenues or at least in 2027
because they recently acquired mirror
and air table which are going to add you
know couple uh I think 1.2 billion or
something. So you can see the older
portfolio without air table and mirror
as a as a black columns here and then
air table and mirror and it adds up to 4
billion per year and so that's when I'm
talking about the existing portfolio
that's what I'm talking about this is
this is the kind of the bunch of assets
that they have and like you know and
here on the on the right side where I'm
showing adjusted operating margins it
shows you that the older portfolio
before Air Table and Mirro they already
run at 40 40 54% margins but Air Table
or Mirro are not there yet because as I
said before it takes you know year or
two before they get all the
transformation going the whole companies
working on their own operating system
and so it takes a bit of time again I'm
a bit more conservative and so I don't
assume that in the first two years they
will reach the 50% and so you can see
that the margins will improve after
that.
>> Right. Of course.
>> So that's their existing portfolio. Now
this is businesses they own. This this
is here you can see actually how much
cash flow they're making each year.
Again, I only assume 2% growth
year-over-year organic for these
companies because the team is quite
honest about they are not necessarily
putting any investments or money into
growing this users base or like this
particular businesses themselves. They
want to grow the whole platform but like
they don't necessarily want to they are
looking for companies that are going to
make cash and like that's their main
focus. So they are not prioritizing
growth which is quite important because
I also think that there is an
opportunity that at some point maybe
when they will not see enough market
opportunities on the market they could
actually just like slow down look at the
companies they own and because they are
able to operate with a huge leverage
meaning they have much better margins
than any other competitor it gives them
advantage. So think of it as
if I if if every one user is more
valuable for me because I have high
margins, I can spend much more money on
one user than my competitors because I
am making more money out of out of that
user. So like it gives them a certain
edge which they could eventually use as
well. But right now they are saying we
are just focus focused on generating
cash. We don't necessarily need all
these companies to grow. And so here I
just assume conservatively that it's
going to keep growing at 2%. Which is
pretty decent. Um and then you know if
that's the assumption
you can see on the right side here for
for the existing businesses what's
what's the value in the bare case based
bull case and base case. That's the
existing business. here is the advantage
that they have against every other kind
of um competitor on the market who might
be interested in acquiring any of these
businesses. So let's say I don't know
Milk Road wants to acquire Mirror or you
know some other company I don't know. So
the real value is that um bending spoons
have built that operating system which
makes them work more efficiently than
anyone else. So if I if I am just like
you know average average not not user
let's say font who is just you know
buying businesses and then trying to
make some restructuring and like make
teams more lean. That's pretty decent.
You can still do it. There's still
upside, don't get me wrong, but I think
what they are trying to do is like
leverage AI because that's really
becoming the new player in this whole
game. And so like that's their kind of
advantage why they are able to, you
know, outbid everyone else. And if
bending spoons participate in auction to
acquire some company, they usually win
because they can afford to, you know,
bid a higher price than anyone else,
>> right? And they can and they can sorry
go back to that slide. So you're saying
I mean this makes a lot of sense but
basically that their ROI for every
dollar spent acquiring a company
is is worth so much more
>> than other potential companies because
of because their business is so unique
at taking software companies and turning
them into winners. And the timeline for
that is usually about a year right or or
roughly.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Here you can see on this
chart I think um for bending spoons
because they are able to like increase
those margins like 30% in in in the year
one 42% in year two and then 50% in year
three and I assume for 90% success. So
like not all acquisitions are successful
but like let's say 90% of them are
because they have seen that playbook
before and they use AI to improve the
internal processes to take advantage of
like the the data they have versus
someone else might be able to like grow
those margins from to 10% and 20 30 and
they might even have a lower success
rate because they're not maybe using AI
that much and again like AI is the game
changer here, right?
>> Mhm.
>> Here's the slide that is probably going
to be um quite interesting to some
people because like everyone thinks that
they'll just keep increasing the the
money spent on the new acquisitions.
And
I think that at some point there's going
to be a limit how much money how much
companies you can buy. And the reason is
not because the team said that there are
thousands of companies that they are
looking at today but over time as more
people and more companies are going to
use the very same strategy. I mean what
bending spoons done like they were the
first pioneer of this but I feel like a
lot of new companies are trying to do
the very same thing. it means that
there's going to be more competition and
the more competition is going to kind of
put more pricing pressure on those new
deals. And so for bending spoons, it
only works if they can acquire these new
businesses like at very reasonable
multiples. So at some point I think
they're going to be maxed out and they
they might not be able to deploy all the
capital they want because they might
need to pay like I think they hurdle
rate is anything below 3x revenue
multiple like below that it means their
hurdle rate which is 25% internal um uh
rate of change but for everything beyond
above three mult revenue multiple it's
not going to make those revenues those
returns so they are just going to not do
it anymore
>> what what is the hurdle rate what
exactly is that
>> the hurdle rate is how much return you
want from your investments
>> okay okay good okay so it's just it's
just the the ROI rate right
>> yes yes um
>> and so there are a certain limits for
how much they can grow um how much spend
uh they do on deals. And again like it's
either because the team is not kind of
scaling enough with with those
acquisitions or maybe there is not
enough debt available or again the
prices of like these software companies
are increasing because there are more
more buyers and they just simply cannot
find the right deals at the right
prices. And like you know it's actually
what we are trying to do here. I love
the business that they are doing. I just
want to make sure that I'm getting this
company at the right price or at least I
want to know what the fair price for
this company should be. So like it's
it's kind of similar analogy here.
>> That makes sense. [clears throat] Okay.
Yeah. So, so and and you also mentioned
earlier on this slide too that
can you can you just circle back on to
how competitors would impact them
because it sounds like it would mainly
drive up the cost like the acquisition
cost because the other thing I guess we
haven't considered too is that this is
such a great business model that other
companies could do it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I think like many other
companies are going to do it. And
>> so like once you have more people like
who are looking at these acquisitions
like at at some point the prices of the
whole of this whole market will just you
know increase because there are more
buyers now. And so here again I am a bit
I think I am a bit conservative. So I am
kind of saying I think at 2031 they will
hit 10 billion and after that I think
they are not just going to be able to
grow like to the infinity and so I kept
it at 10 billion like for the next 5
years. Again like those are my
assumptions like anyone can you know if
you are more bullish and you think that
they are going to be able to find those
those deals you know at reasonable
prices even like after maybe. So again
I'm I do not think that will be that
easy in you know 5 years. This slide
actually uh shows exactly what I was
talking about. So at some point you on
the left on the left chart you can see
the hurl rate. So like they are not
going to buy companies above this kind
of price. So if revenue multiples are
above three, they're not going to do it
because it just doesn't fit their
strategy and it doesn't match their
returns that they expect from these
deals. So that's why I kept that at at
um uh 10 billion per year. And on the
right side, you can see the learnings.
New deals get better with experience
which means like I think I put like
every time they double their revenues
their margins will improve by one
percentage point because like the more
the more uh transactions you do the more
businesses you kind of bring to your
platform the better you get as a result
as a platform as a whole right so like
that's how um I think this should be
somehow reflected as well so like maybe
at the beginning you know they are able
to operate at let's say 50% margins but
as they see more data more businesses
joining then their margins are improving
as more businesses are on the platform
>> right so they compound they can compound
their business because they can just
yeah because they have so much data and
customers that as they like they become
more efficient and they can do more and
and have their business their I guess
these portfolio companies that they own
they can like crossromote or find more
customers for them over time because
they have so much more data and they
become kind of like a conglomerate
almost of these types of companies.
>> Yeah, I think they do not like uh the
idea of cross-selling because you know
it might be a different businesses but
like generally like when you have the
platform that like everyone is building
on top of you you'll get a lot of
different use cases and different ideas
you can iterate much quicker than anyone
else. And so like it gives you a certain
advantages that you you would not be
able to get if you if you are solo.
>> That makes sense.
>> So on this slide here um because I did
the projections for the the next 10
years but because the full transition
takes you know uh two or three three
years. So the the whole uh time frame
here is all the way until 2039
which seems like you know insane but
like you know I think for the next 10
years it makes sense and then it just
like I I wanted just the model to kind
of finalize like all all the businesses
that were acquired in 20 36 or 37 to
kind of transform and kind of reach the
final kind of state. So they are fully
transformed and operating on the
platform and so you can see here the c
cash flow how is it going to evolve over
time and I think it's it's pretty decent
again assuming like everything goes as
as I was just you know saying about and
on the right chart here you can see
group adjusted margins which is
the current margins and um of the
current portfolio plus the new acquired
businesses is and you can see a kind of
a jump down here in in 2028 and it's
mainly because um they just acquired
Mirror and Air Table and so they are
still not operating at full full full
margins at the final kind of numbers
that they want them to have. Plus they
are going to you know acquire like other
businesses next year and so they are
also going to operate at much lower
margins than the target. But at some
point like those new new deals will
become less relevant and like the whole
group operating margins will just keep
growing up and also because the the
compounding effects I've been talking
about. So you you need economies of
scale and so those will improve their
margins as a as a company as well. Okay,
here's the debt. I was talking just
quickly about depth and like some people
will see that at 20 35 I can see that
they might be about 39 billion in depth
for the company. So you know it might be
scary for some people but again like
they are buying companies and those
companies are quickly turned into pretty
profitable money machines. So it's very
different than if you are buying you
know um I don't want to say GPUs but um
when you are buying something else that
like your your demand or like your
returns are you know less likely or like
more at risk rather than here when you
are buying companies with real users and
some most of them are already
profitable. they just do not have as
high margins that they could have and so
um debt levels are going to be high but
again it's not really a concern. Team
said that they want to keep the the
leverage about 3x and right now they're
like pretty maxed out because they just
did IPO and then they also acquired
Mirror and they paid with um their own
stocks issuance. So, um it looks pretty
bad right now, but it's not really that
bad. And the debt is again just 5
billion. So, it's pretty decent. They're
going to make um 1 billion plus in in
cash next year. So, um it's pretty
doable. But o over the long term,
they're targeting 3x leverage. This is
what I was talking about earlier. The
team is looking like their target for
each acquisition is unlevered irr which
is internal rate of return and so it
needs to meet that 50 uh 25% if not they
are not making the deal and so if we are
looking just at um return on investment
it should be above 11% because again
this is one of the inputs what investors
demand that the company will bring each
year like what's the return and I think
like maybe You could argue that it
should be higher or lower, but I think I
feel like 11% is is pretty decent. So,
what you guys see here right now, the
the the price of the stock is 33 bucks,
but if you if you deduct the the the tax
shield and if you deduct the existing
portfolio they own, you'll get $15,
which means that the whole kind of
future deal machine and cash machine is
worth only 15 bucks. But again, I think
in my base case that should be worth
like 30 bucks. So that's the upside. And
here on the right side, you can actually
kind of challenge that. And those are
two assumptions that you need to make.
One is
what is the return that shareholders are
going to demand for that cash? Like what
are the returns that investors are going
to demand? And so like again in my base
case, I use 11%. So we are looking at
the the black line here and here on the
uh on the x-axis those are the exit
multiples of cash flows. So I used 12
multiple of free cash flows saying that
I think the each of these companies
would be able to exit at 12x
of their cash that they are making. So,
but you know maybe you are more bullish
or you are more conservative. So like
find your line here and you will get the
price.
>> Why 12?
>> It's pretty decent. I think like it's
it's the lower end of like um how
software companies are valued. So they
are usually in the range of 10 to 18 or
something like that. So I I I put 12.
Um, I want again I think it's it's a bit
it's a it's a it's definitely on the
lower end and a bit more conservative
and I can imagine pretty easily that
it's going to be trading much much
higher and the reason is that
I feel like more and more companies are
now trading more on their stories or
narratives like how sexy the story is
like look at Tesla or Palunteer you like
you would never buy those companies if
you are just thinking about like 12x
cash multiples like you know they are
they are not even making cash so like
you know it just doesn't make sense um
so I think I'm pretty conservative here
and again the the bull side the bull
case is that
>> it will become a market darling and like
you know investors will just buy no
matter what because the story is super
compelling And that's the bullcase. And
I really like it because I am usually
the guy who is saying like, "Oh, this is
super expensive. I'm not touching the
never." And like yes, but like you
should ignore valuation like markets
going to love this because of the story
is so good and yeah blah blah. I I I
don't buy it usually. So here in this
case, I love this company because the
base case is also giving me a certain
upside where I I I think the downside is
still limited because of the businesses
they already own and the bull side the
bull case the call option like that the
stock will go to the moon is that the
the market will really like it because
the story is again pretty pretty
compelling. Do you see a world where and
I guess this is more from a almost like
a like a marketing standpoint or or
would be good to kind of get them into
the mainstream because this is a really
unknown company. Is there a world where
they would buy like a really big
software giant that is just doing so
poorly like bigger than any of the
companies they've bought they've bought
previously? You know what I mean to make
like a really big splash and acquire
like a huge bucket of users?
>> Yeah. I think um
>> I don't know who I don't know who I'm
talking about. Like I don't know. I
don't think they I don't think they'd
buy Salesforce. You know what I mean?
That's if Salesforce is always our most
like basic example. But I just mean like
some of the companies you mentioned like
these are those are decent sized
companies, right? But they're not
they're not that upper tier of SAS
companies, but that I wonder if these
guys could do that in the future and
that would really kind of put them on
the map and kind of start that, you
know, kind of premium price pump like
you're saying that becomes like a market
darling.
>> Probably not Salesforce because it's
>> it's not this is a bad example.
>> It's a giant. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I can imagine that they would buy
someone like relatively big market cap
because again like you know bending
spoon is 23 billion market cap or
something like that. So I can imagine
that they would buy at some point
someone worth you know um
not not hundreds but probably tens of
millions and it's certainly doable and I
think that's actually where they are
looking at like when they are heading
because in in some podcast I believe
that the the CEO said something like now
they are trying to look for kind of
bigger bigger fishes and and so it feels
like they that's what they want to And
it makes sense because they said the the
transformation time doesn't scale with
revenue. So it doesn't matter if you buy
company that makes 100 billions in
revenue or if we buy a company that
makes you know 1 billion revenue. It it
it doesn't change like the the timeline
for the transformation. So that's that's
actually pretty pretty attractive
because it just makes sense for them to
buy someone you know who is making much
more money. Uh because then the the
operating leverage is is gonna uh just
play in our
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. That makes sense.
Yeah. Cool. Okay. So, Martin, is this
something that is in your in your pro
portfolio?
>> Uh not yet. It's on my watch list.
Listen, the market right now is really
hard to read and um I actually sold some
of my positions uh I think last week and
also a couple weeks ago. So, I'm right
now more in defensive mode where I'm
just worried about what's going to
happen next because yes, some AI stocks
might do well, but the rest of the
markets, if you look at the other
sectors, like pretty much all of them
are going down. And so, it's only a few
stocks that are kind of driving the
whole S&P or NASDAQ index up. And it's
and then you have yields at, you know,
5.2 or 5.3 record levels in 20 years.
you have oil like there are so many
things going on so I don't necessarily
want to kind of deploy any any capital
at this moment because I feel very
uncertain about where markets are
heading next.
>> Mhm. Yeah, that's very cautious and I
think that that's something that you've
been you've very much been leading I
would say at Milk Road in terms of in
terms of exercising that caution ahead
of what could be a bit of a turbulent
time especially going up to midterms and
everything that's going on. But good to
know that it is on your watch list and
and for people that want to know when
Martin will deploy into this if he does.
Um I mean you've made a very compelling
bull case and this company clearly has
like a really bright future and a huge
head start and a really good moat on on
any competitors. So uh anybody wants to
follow that it's on Milk Road Pro and
check it out at the link below. Uh
anything else Martin before we wrap up
that we should know about this company?
>> No I I I would say stay tuned because me
and Winston we love this company. We
keep learning more about them like every
day. Um, from time to time we share some
updates on our Milk Road platform as
well. And so, um, yeah. Um, just stay
tuned.
>> Excellent. Well, thank you, Martin.
Great show, man.
>> Thank you. It was fun.
>> Thanks for listening to Milk Road. If
you enjoyed the show, make sure you like
and subscribe. [music] And if you're
struggling to find winners in the
market, that's exactly what Milkroad Pro
is built for. Our analysts [music] have
called some of the biggest winners early
and Pro lets you see what they're buying
next, every trade they make, and the
research behind [music] every position.
Check out Milk Road Pro at the link
below. Everything you hear on Milkroad
is forformational purposes only. [music]
These are our personal opinions, not
financial advice, and we may own some of
the investments we talk about. Always do
your own research and make the decisions
that are right for you. See you next
time.